Staaare
It's too heavy! I can't carry it!
Hahahaha
Panda Coffee
Juumart
Post Office
Kids' Park
Tawson
Kitsune
Acupuncture
Yatsubishi Bank
Mutsunomiya Branch
Souma
Building
Chomp chomp
Smack
Ngahhhh
Thump-thump-thump
Hey,
don't
do
that!
We're going demon
hunting later today
m 0 0 l 185 0 l 185 70 l 0 70
I have a tummy ache
m 0 0 l 185 0 l 185 40 l 0 40
Akutsu
Did you eat something
off the floor?
Judgment rendered!
Shape up your tummy!
Gives you nice curves
Family Life
Getting
Your
Child
to
Grow
Yet, they bought them
Hey, are you there?
Answer me, servant
Are you staying put in bed?
Aids           growth
Strawberry milk flavor
Senovil
My First
Purikura
I'm fine now.
Where are you?
Fine. Stay in bed for today
Take your medicine
And contact me when you're better